

# Ecommerce & CRM Specialist

**MAI NGOC LE VY** 

A skilled operation associate with extensive experience in the ecommerce and Fin-tech industry, I am proficient in the operation management, build relationship with third-parties and user experience in company's product. I want to utilize my skills to make significant contributions to your organization.

## CONTACT

0902-734-801

HCMC, Vietnam

levimai2007@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/levymai/

### EDUCATION

**Ton Duc Thang University** 2017 - 2021

Bachelor's Degree in **Bussiness Administration** 

#### SKILLS

**Project Management** 

Data analysis and presentation

Communication

Multi-tasking







Diagrams Salesforce









Google Sheets Looker Studio Google Slides

# EXPERIENCE

# **Customer Service - BPO Operations Management**

MoMo - Mobile Service Joint Stock Comapny I Oct 2023 - Present

- Play a key role in managing BPO vendor with 40 agents support user in multi-channel (Call Center, Email, Chat, App). Lead and manage team resources to ensure real-time KPI, SLA and performance.
- Take ownership of SLA, ensure real-time process, monitor productivity, inbound volume and reach 90% utilization rate and 85% CSAT (nearly 7000 contacts per day)
- Work closely with vendors in dealing contract terms, review hiring and onboarding newbies to ensure qualified candidates.
- Develop data-driven strategies and summarize inflow trends to enhance the suppliers capability and save company cost.
- Utilize product knowledge to verify issues and accompany with business leaders from CS team to provide solutions for customer's queries regarding account, transactions, etc
- · Prepare and forecast annual budget for business partners and find solutions for improving metrics, along with making plans to optimize working flow plus reduce expenses.

#### **Content Operations**

ShopeeFood - Shopee Vietnam - SEA Limited I Dec 2021 - Oct 2023

- Managed content/meu display on internal system and external application of all ShopeeFood sellers with accepted criteria.
- Built and conducted SOP to reduce 30% lead time onboarding with nearly 1,000 new merchants successfully activated per week.
- Coordinated with +200 BD nationwide plus other stakeholders to consolidate and optimize onboarding workflow. As a result, saved cost and BPO's resource (5 HCs in Q4-2022)
- Acted as a bridge between Partnership and Marketing team to setting up and executing monthly campaign for sellers.
- Identified struggles in seller's operations and proposed iniatives to cross functional team to enhance their experience and utilize self-help options.